Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - E-H
        - Earland, Charles - Earland's jam, 1982; SR-24624; Earland, Charles (Box 29)
          Catalog # FC 37573; A-side Matrix # AL-37573-1A
          Columbia
          New York, New York
        - Earland, Charles - Over & over; I like it, 1978; SR-24625; Earland, Charles (Box 29)
          Promo
          Catalog # MK-58; A-side Matrix # MK-58A-2
          Mercury
        - Earland, Charles - Be my lady (tonight), 1983; SR-24626; Earland, Charles (Box 29)
          Catalog # AS 1609; A-side Matrix # XSS-170797-1B
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - I am, 1979; SR-24627; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # FC 35730; A-side Matrix # PAL-35730-1AA
          ARC
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Raise!, 1981; SR-24628; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # TC 37548; A-side Matrix # PAL-37548-1G
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Moment of truth, 1971; SR-24629; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # SSP 3078; A-side Matrix # SSP 3078 W-6
          Pickwick Super Stars
          London, United Kingdom
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Let's groove, 1981; SR-24630; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # AS 1304; A-side Matrix # XSS-168315-1C
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Faces (disc one), 1980; SR-24631; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24632. Double album.
          Catalog # KC2 36795; A-side Matrix # PAL-36796-1AH
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Faces (disc two), 1980; SR-24632; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24631. Double album.
          Catalog # KC2 36795; A-side Matrix # PAL-36797-2H
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Spirit, 1976; SR-24633; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # PC 34241; A-side Matrix # T2 PAL 34241 1G
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Gratitude, 1975; SR-24634; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24635. Double album.
          Catalog # PG 33694; A-side Matrix # AL 33695 F-A
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - Gratitude, 1975; SR-24635; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24634. Double album.
          Catalog # PG 33694; A-side Matrix # PAL 33696-1N
        - Earth, Wind & Fire - That's the way of the world, 1975; SR-25082; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 29)
          Catalog # PC 33280; A-side Matrix # PAL 33280 1C
        - East - East, 1972; SR-24636; East (Box 29)
          Catalog # ST-11083; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11083-F6
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - East Bam - Aka aka, 1990; SR-24637; East Bam (Box 29)
          Catalog # 12 YOBR 1; A-side Matrix # 12 YOBR 1 A-1U-1-1
          Yo*Bro Recordings
        - Eastbound Expressway - Eastbound Expressway, 1979; SR-24638; Eastbound Expressway (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24639. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # AVI-6068; A-side Matrix # 059-6068-A-PRC-1-11-1
          AVI Records
        - Eastbound Expressway - Eastbound Expressway, 1979; SR-24639; Eastbound Expressway (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24638. 2 copies. Promo
        - Easton, Sheena - The lover in me, 1988; SR-24640; Easton, Sheena (Box 29)
          Catalog # MCA-42249; A-side Matrix # MCA8300 FDS-2
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Easy Earl - The boulevard brut; Easiest the earl, 1988; SR-24641; Easy Earl; DJ Fantasy B; L.G.; Street Rapper Godzilla; Aggravated Assault (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24642. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RR-001; A-side Matrix # RR-001-A
          Ray Ray Records
          Queens, New York
        - Easy Earl - The boulevard brut; Easiest the earl, 1988; SR-24642; Easy Earl; DJ Fantasy B; L.G.; Street Rapper Godzilla; Aggravated Assault (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24641. 2 copies.
        - Easy Going - Baby I love you; Suzie Q, 1979; SR-24643; Easy Going (Box 29)
          Catalog # PDS 4; A-side Matrix # PDS-4A-RE
          Prism
        - Easy Street - Under the glass, 1977; SR-24644; Easy Street (Box 29)
          Catalog # CP 0184; A-side Matrix # CP-1-0184 LW2
          Capricorn Records
          Macon, Georgia
        - Eboman - Sampling madness 1 - donuts with Buddah (disc one), 1996; SR-24645; Eboman (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24646. Double album.
          Catalog # XLEP 123; A-side Matrix # XLEP123 A1
          XL Recordings
        - Eboman - Sampling madness 1 - donuts with Buddah (disc one), 1996; SR-24646; Eboman (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24645. Double album.
          Catalog # XLEP 123; A-side Matrix # XLEP123 C1
        - Ebonee Webb - Ebonee Webb, 1981; SR-24647; Ebonee Webb (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24648. Different discs.
          Catalog # ST-12148; A-side Matrix # B-15773 ST-1-12148-Z3
        - Ebonee Webb - Something about you, 1981; SR-24648; Ebonee Webb (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24647. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-9689; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9689-97619-Z1
        - Ebony Rhythm Funk Campaign - Ebony Rhythm Funk Campaign, 1973; SR-24649; Ebony Rhythm Funk Campaign (Box 29)
          Catalog # 73142; A-side Matrix # 73142 A W2
          UNI Records
        - Echo & The Bunnymen - Bedbugs And Ballyhoo, 1987; SR-24650; Echo & The Bunnymen (Box 29)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2977; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2977-SH-1 B-30157-SH1 19363 1-1
          Sire
        - Eclipse - Night and day, 1977; SR-24651; Eclipse (Box 29)
          Catalog # NBLP 7097; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7097-AS CP-1
          Casablanca
          Los Angeles, California
        - Edikanfo - The pace setters, 1981; SR-24652; Edikanfo (Box 29)
          Catalog # EGM 112; A-side Matrix # EGM-112-A-RE-1
          Editions EG
          South Plainfield, New Jersey
        - Edima, Tity - Medim me yom, SR-24653; Edima, Tity (Box 29)
          Catalog # DPX 823; A-side Matrix # MPO DPX 823 A1
          Dragon Phénix
          France
        - Edwards, Bernard - Glad to be here, 1983; SR-24654; Edwards, Bernard (Box 29)
          Catalog # 80079-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-835205-D RL 1-1
          Atlantic
        - Edwards, Dee - Two hearts are better than one, 1980; SR-24655; Edwards, Dee (Box 29)
          Catalog # SD 5223; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-804539-A
          Cotillion
        - Edwards, Max - Rockers arena, 1982; SR-24656; Edwards, Max (Box 29)
          Catalog # ELP 4020; A-side Matrix # ELP 4020A 14478(3)
          Epiphany Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Egyptian Lover - On the Nile, 1984; SR-24657; Egyptian Lover (Box 29)
          Catalog # DMSR-0663; A-side Matrix # L-10232-00663-A
          Egyptian Empire Records ‎
        - Egyptian Lover - King of ecstasy (his greatest hits album), 1989; SR-24658; Egyptian Lover (Box 29)
          Catalog # DMSR 883; A-side Matrix # 680-DMSR 883-1 CA1 S-45654
          Egyptian Empire Records
        - Egyptian Lover - King of ecstasy (his greatest hits album), 1989; SR-24659; Egyptian Lover (Box 29)
          Catalog # DMSR 883; A-side Matrix # 681-DSMR 883-1(C) S-45656
        - Einstein - Gotstago, 1989; SR-24660; Einstein (Box 29)
          Catalog # NOTE 31; A-side Matrix # NOTE-31-A1
          Music Of Life
          United Kingdom
        - Electro City Funksterz - KHz E.P, 2000; SR-24661; Electro City Funksterz (Box 29)
          Catalog # SS002; A-side Matrix # 08 43270 20 1A1 SS 002 TTT
          Sound Surgery Records
        - Elecktroids - Elektroworld, 1995; SR-24662; Elecktroids (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24663. Double album.
          Catalog # WARP LP 35; A-side Matrix # WARPLP-35-A1
          Warp Records
        - Elecktroids - Elektroworld, 1995; SR-24663; Elecktroids (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24662. Double album.
          Catalog # WARP LP 35; A-side Matrix # WARPLP-35-C1
        - Eleventh Hour - Greatest hits 1974 AD, 1974; SR-24664; Eleventh Hour (Box 29)
          Catalog # T-435; A-side Matrix # M 435 AS
          20th Century Records
        - Elite - Rock the house, 1980; SR-24665; Elite (Box 29)
          Catalog # DK 101; A-side Matrix # 1-202-1A
          Dakar Records
        - Elliott, Missy - Miss E …so addictive (disc one), 2001; SR-24666; Elliott, Missy (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24667. Double album.
          Catalog # 62639-1; A-side Matrix # STED-6289 A-1
          Elektra
        - Elliott, Missy - Miss E …so addictive (disc two), 2001; SR-24667; Elliott, Missy (Box 29)
          In same jacket as # SR-24666. Double album.
          Catalog # 62639-1; A-side Matrix # STED 6289 C1
        - Ellis, Shirley - The name game, 1965; SR-24668; Ellis, Shirley (Box 29)
          Catalog # CGL-3003; A-side Matrix # MONO CGL 5 3003-A-1
          Congress
        - Elusion - All toys break, 1981; SR-24669; Elusion (Box 29)
          Catalog # SD 16040; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-814651-E O-35M1-2
        - Emotions - Come into our world, 1979; SR-24670; Emotions (Box 29)
          Catalog # JC 36149; A-side Matrix # PAL-36149-1D
        - Emotions - New affair, 1981; SR-24671; Emotions (Box 29)
          Catalog # FC 37456; A-side Matrix # PAL-37456-1H
        - Empress - Dyin' to be dancin', 1981; SR-24674; Empress (Box 29)
          Catalog # PRL D 607; A-side Matrix # PRLD-607AS-1A
          Prelude Records
        - Enchantment - Soft lights, sweet music, 1980; SR-24675; Enchantment (Box 29)
          Catalog # AFL1-3824; A-side Matrix # AFL-1-3824-A-3
          RCA Victor
        - End II Deep - Deep in the pocket, 2002; SR-24676; End II Deep (Box 29)
          Catalog # E2D001; A-side Matrix # E2D001-A
          End II Deep
          Alexandria, Virginia
        - Energetics - Come down to earth, 1979; SR-24677; Energetics (Box 29)
          Catalog # SD 19224; A-side Matrix # STA-784213-B
        - English, Barbara Jean - Barbara Jean English, 1973; SR-25003; English, Barbara Jean (Box 29)
          Catalog # AR-9105; A-side Matrix # AR 9105-A
          Alithia
          Bergen, New Jersey
        - English Beat - Wha'ppen, 1981; SR-24678; English Beat (Box 29)
          Catalog # SRK 3567; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-3567-JW1
        - Eno - Taking Tiger Mountain (by strategy), 1974; SR-24679; Eno; Eno, Brian (Box 29)
          Catalog # ILPS 9309; A-side Matrix # S ILPS 9309-A 1 SXT
          Island Records
        - Eno, Brian - My life in the bush of ghosts, 1981; SR-24680; Eno, Brian; Byrne, David (Box 30)
          Catalog # SRK 6093; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-6093-RE1-LW1
        - Entouch - All nite, 1989; SR-24681; Entouch (Box 30)
          Catalog # 60858-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60858-A1
        - Entwistle, John - Too late the hero, 1981; SR-24682; Entwistle, John (Box 30)
          Catalog # PR 398; A-side Matrix # ST PR 40293-5
          ATCO Records
        - EPMD - Unfinished business, 1989; SR-24683; EPMD (Box 30)
          Catalog # LPRE-92012; A-side Matrix # LPRE-92012-X-DMM SP1-2
          Fresh Records
        - Equals - Doin' the 45's, 1984; SR-24684; Equals; Grant, Eddy (Box 30)
          Catalog # 20047; A-side Matrix # 20047-A
          Astan
          West-Germany
          Switzerland
        - Equitables - Rocking Soca, SR-24685; Equitables (Box 30)
          Catalog # GS2264; A-side Matrix # GS2264A
          Straker's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - ESG - ESG says dance to the beat of moody, SR-24686; ESG (Box 30)
          Catalog # 99-10EP; A-side Matrix # 99-10 EP-B
          99 Records
        - Etch & Sketch Boyz - C12 matter; Clap you hands: We wanna play, 1997; SR-24687; Etch & Sketch Boyz; C12 (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24688. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DRP121997; A-side Matrix # DRP-12-1A
          Drop Records
        - Etch & Sketch Boyz - C12 matter; Clap you hands: We wanna play, 1997; SR-24688; Etch & Sketch Boyz; C13 (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24687. 2 copies.
        - EU - Nasty, 1993; SR-24689; EU; 151 (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24690. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # ND/G 3500; A-side Matrix # ND/G-3500-A
          ND/Goff Records
        - EU - Make some noise; At the Go Go, 1992; SR-24690; EU (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24689. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # ND/G 3504; A-side Matrix # ND/G-3504-A
        - Experienced Unlimited - Somebody's ringing that doorbell (express yourself), 1982; SR-24691; Experienced Unlimited; EU; Sugar Bear (Box 30)
          Catalog # IC 7009; A-side Matrix # 7009-A
          Inner City Records Of Washington D.C.
          Washington DC, United States
        - Eurythmics - Touch dance, 1984; SR-24692; Eurythmics (Box 30)
          Catalog # PG 70354; A-side Matrix # B-1149 A-4
          RCA
          Germany
        - Evans, Richard - Richard Evans, 1979; SR-24693; Evans, Richard (Box 30)
          Catalog # SP-735; A-side Matrix # T-1 SP-769 T-2
          Horizon
        - Everlast - Eat at Whitey's (disc one), 2000; SR-24694; Everlast (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24695. Double album.
          Catalog # TB1411; A-side Matrix # TB-1411-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Everlast - Eat at Whitey's (disc two), 2000; SR-24695; Everlast (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24694. Double album.
          Catalog # TB1411; A-side Matrix # TB-1411-C
        - Everyday People - Everyday People, 1971; SR-24696; Everyday People (Box 30)
          Catalog # PAS-6021; A-side Matrix # PAS-6021-A-6
          Paramount Records
        - Evil Nine - Technology; Big game hunter, 2000; SR-24697; Evil Nine (Box 30)
          Catalog # MAPA010; A-side Matrix # MAPA 010 A-2
          Marine Parade
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Evil Nine - Cakehole, 2002; SR-24698; Evil Nine (Box 30)
          Catalog # MAPA0017; A-side Matrix # MAPA 017 A1
        - Executive Slacks - Fire & ice, 1986; SR-24699; Executive Slacks (Box 30)
          Catalog # SAVE9; A-side Matrix # SAVE-11-A
          Fundamental
          Covington, Georgia
        - Exotic Storm - In the beginning, 1986; SR-24700; Exotic Storm (Box 30)
          Catalog # BFE 40427; A-side Matrix # PAL-40427-1A
          Epic
        - Exportations - Meet the Exportations, 1978; SR-24701; Exportations (Box 30)
          Catalog # UA-LA872-H; A-side Matrix # UA-LA-872-1
          United Artists Records
        - Exuma - Exuma II (Air), 1970; SR-24702; Exuma (Box 30)
          Catalog # SR-61314; A-side Matrix # SR61314-A-M1
        - Exuma - Exuma, 1970; SR-24703; Exuma (Box 30)
          Catalog # SR-61265; A-side Matrix # SR61265-1-A6
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Fabe - Befa surprend ses frères (disc one), 1995; SR-24704; Fabe (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24705. Double album.
          Catalog # 528119-1; A-side Matrix # UR 15 LP A1 SNA 528273-1-A
          Shaman
        - Fabe - Befa surprend ses frères (disc two), 1995; SR-24705; Fabe (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24704. Double album.
          Catalog # 528119-1; A-side Matrix # UR 15 LP C1 SNA 528273-1-A
        - Fabe - Befa surprend ses frères (disc one), 1995; SR-24706; Fabe (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24707. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 15 LP; A-side Matrix # UR 15 LP A1 SNA
          Unik Records
        - Fabe - Befa surprend ses frères (disc two), 1995; SR-24707; Fabe (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24706. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 15 LP; A-side Matrix # UR 15 LP C1 SNA
        - Fabulous Fantoms - Just having a party, 2001; SR-24708; Fabulous Fantoms (Box 30)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0035; A-side Matrix # DELLP-0035A
          Funky Delicacies
        - Fabulous Peps - Detroit, Michigan, 2000; SR-24709; Fabulous Peps (Box 30)
          Catalog # STS LP 6348; A-side Matrix # STS LP 6348-A
          Soul-Tay-Shus
        - Fabulous Souls - Take Me | The Thought Of Losing Your Love, 2002; SR-24710; Fabulous Souls; Ebony Rhythm Band (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24711. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NA-2001; A-side Matrix # NA-2001A
          Lamp Records
          Bloomington, Indiana
        - Fabulous Souls - Take Me | The Thought Of Losing Your Love, 2002; SR-24711; Fabulous Souls; Ebony Rhythm Band (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24710. 2 copies.
        - Facade - The groove, 1985; SR-24712; Facade (Box 30)
          Catalog # THR-4; A-side Matrix # L10416 THR-4A
          Techno Hop Records
          Paramount, California
        - Fadela, Chaba - You are mine, 1988; SR-24713; Fadela, Chaba (Box 30)
          Catalog # MLPS 9827; A-side Matrix # MLPS 9827-A
          Mango
        - Failsafe - A fistful of failsafe, SR-24714; Failsafe (Box 30)
          Catalog # PRS 0002; A-side Matrix # PRS 0002-A PRC-C-1-1
          Paris Records
        - Faison - Love fire, 1981; SR-24715; Faison (Box 30)
          Catalog # EPLP 504; A-side Matrix # EPLP-504 Side 1-A-2 PRC
          Erect Records
          Merrillville, Indiana
        - Faith Hope & Charity - Faith Hope & Charity, 1978; SR-24716; Faith Hope & Charity (Box 30)
          Catalog # T-560; A-side Matrix # M-560-AS-SM-4
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Faithfull, Marianne - Dangerous acquaintances, 1981; SR-24717; Faithfull, Marianne (Box 30)
          Catalog # ILPS 9648; A-side Matrix # L927 B-16150-S1 ILPS-1 9648-S1
          Burbank, California
        - Fakroun, Ahmed - Mots d'amour, 1987; SR-24718; Fakroun, Ahmed (Box 30)
          Catalog # 66835-1; A-side Matrix # CEL 66835-1-A
          Celluloid
        - Falco - Einzelhaft, 1982; SR-24719; Falco (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24720. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AMLH 68550; A-side Matrix # NL 19-68550-1A-1
          A&M Records
          Holland
        - Falco - Einzelhaft, 1982; SR-24720; Falco (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24719. 2 copies.
        - Falco - Emotional, 1986; SR-24721; Falco (Box 30)
          Catalog # 1-25522; A-side Matrix # 1 25522 A SH2
        - Faline, Tony - Feel the funk, 2000; SR-24722; Faline, Tony (Box 30)
          Catalog # UN 018; A-side Matrix # UNION 018
          Union Records
          Sarasota, Florida
        - Family Circle - Love bound, 1977; SR-24723; Family Circle (Box 30)
          Catalog # STW 6002; A-side Matrix # STW 6002-A K-7753
          Strawberry Records
        - Family Players - I love funk 'n' roll, 1982; SR-24724; Family Players (Box 30)
          Catalog # MCA-5356; A-side Matrix # MCA-3165-W4
        - Fancy - Check it out, 1985; SR-24725; Fancy (Box 30)
          Catalog # P49818; A-side Matrix # P49818A-1A
          Personal Records
        - Fania All Stars - Rhythm machine, 1977; SR-24726; Fania All Stars (Box 30)
          Catalog # PC 34711; A-side Matrix # AL 34711-1A
        - Fania All Stars - Cross over, 1979; SR-24727; Fania All Stars (Box 30)
          Catalog # JC 36109; A-side Matrix # AL-36109-1D
        - Fania All Stars - Hot sweat (the best of Fania All Stars live) (disc one), 2005; SR-24728; Fania All Stars (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24729. Double album.
          Catalog # VAMPI 046; A-side Matrix # 59923E1-A
          Vampi Soul
          Madrid, Spain
        - Fania All Stars - Hot sweat (the best of Fania All Stars live) (disc two), 2005; SR-24729; Fania All Stars (Box 30)
          In same jacket as # SR-24728. Double album.
          Catalog # VAMPI 046; A-side Matrix # 59923E3-A
        - Fantastic Four - Night people, 1976; SR-24730; Fantastic Four (Box 30)
          Catalog # W-226; A-side Matrix # M226-AS TM/JR
          Westbound Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Fantastique - Fantastique, 1982; SR-24731; Fantastique (Box 30)
          Catalog # 495.055; A-side Matrix # 495 055 1Y 1 670
          CNR